aytm.com 2018-12-02

# Online Market Research | AYTM Market Research

If you are a resident of the EU or a country which adheres to the GDPR, please refer to our EU PRIVACY POLICY. 

###  About Us: 

Umongous, Inc. (" **Umongous** " the " **Company** " " **we** " or " **us** ") is a privately held market research company, with headquarters in San Francisco, CA. Umongous recognizes that its visitors, users, members and others who use AYTM.com, ASKYOURTARGETMARKET.COM, or other websites owned or operated by the Company (the " **Website** ") value their privacy (collectively or individually "Users" or "you"). This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Website when you purchase or otherwise use market research services ("Services") on our Website and your choices regarding this information. 

###  What Information We Collect: 

Information We Collect Directly From You: 

  * **Registration Information:** Users wishing to purchase Services must first successfully register with us through the Website (" **Registration** "). The Registration process will require that you provide us with your legal name, a valid, verifiable email address, your company name (optional), password, type of business, where you heard about us and the time zone in which you are located. 
  * **Billing information:** If you make a payment to Umongous, you would need to provide billing information, such as a name, address, email address and financial information corresponding to your selected method of payment (e.g. a credit card number and expiration date or a bank account number). We use a third-party provider for the processing of the payment information and do not have access to your payment card information. 
  * **Survey data.** We store your survey data (such as questions and responses) for you. If you include personal information in your survey questions, those will be disclosed to the survey takers. 
  * **Other information you choose to share.**  
When you communicate with us: We may collect your personal information or data if you voluntarily submit it to us. For example, if your personal information is included in your communications to us, including via email or other communications channels.  
When you comment on a blog or offer a testimonial: If you comment on our blogs or agree to provide a customer testimonial or review. Please be aware that these are public areas of our Website and any information you provide in these areas might be read, collected, and used by others who access them. If you provide a testimonial, you name will be posted along with the testimonial.  
When you use the chat feature: If you take advantage of our live chat feature to receive technical support or ask general questions regarding use of our platform we retain copies of the live chats. If our live chat is offline we will collect your name and email address so that we may reply to your request through our support desk. 

Information We Collect Indirectly About You: 

When you use our Website as a visitor or as User with a registered account, we may collect the information described below about you indirectly and passively: 

  * **Usage Information:** We collect information about your use of the Website and the Services including which webpages you visit, what you click on, when you performed those actions etc. We also collect log information which includes: IP address, time a page was viewed, browser type, URL parameters, and information from cookies (as described below). 
  * **Device Information:** We use "digital fingerprinting", a technology used to place a unique identifier on the mobile device or computer you use in connection with the Services. We use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that this digital fingerprinting technology is safe, secure and does not cause egregious privacy or data security risks. We also collect information such as your IP address, operating system version, device type, system and performance information, and browser type. 
  * **Information from other third parties:** We may collect your personal information from third parties if you give such third parties permission to share your information with us. For example, we may receive your name and billing address from the third-party payment processors we use to make payments to you. 
  * **Information from cookies and similar technologies:**  
Our research, technology, and marketing partners, affiliates, analytics, service or, incentive delivery providers, etc. use "cookies" during your sessions. Cookies are small amounts of data which are sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer or device. We use cookies to store Website member login credentials automatically if voluntarily elected by the member. Our web server also creates cookies to uniquely identify each User session when a Website member visits the Website. You can choose to disable cookies on your browser (see below) but doing so may prevent you from using the full features of the Website.  
We use web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) along with cookies, to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how the Website is used, and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.  
For information about your choices regarding these technologies please see "Your Access and Choices regarding your Personal Information" below. 

###  How we use your information: 

We may use your information to: 

  * **Provide you the Services: This includes:** providing you with survey statistics and detailed survey results, providing you with technical support, sending you communications in connection with the Services, responding to your requests and administering your account. You may opt-out from receiving these emails by selecting the opt-out link in the email. If you opt out of service-related emails then we have no way of providing purchase receipts, notifications of survey completions/errors and/or notification of payment errors. 
  * **Maintain, Monitor and improve our Services:** We use usage and other information to help maintain our Website and to analyze how you use the Website and Services, including how you interact with different parts of the Website, whether you open emails or click on links in them. This enables us to assess the effectiveness of our marketing efforts, to determine products that are suitable for you and to improve our Website and Services and your experience with them, for example through the optimization of the Website's layout and otherwise enhancing your navigation through the Website. 
  * **Maintain the safety and security of our services:** We may use your information for internal purposes designed to keep our Services secure and operational, such as for troubleshooting and testing purposes. For example: certain cookies we use store user credential automatically, to remember users' settings and protect unauthorized access. 
  * **Prevent illegal or abusive conduct.** We use your information as necessary to enforce our terms of use and privacy policy, to help prevent illicit or illegal use of the Website or the services, and to screen for and prevent undesirable or abusive activity. For example, we have automated systems that screen content for phishing activities, spam, and fraud. In addition, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond to legal requests or subpoenas. 
  * **Marketing and Advertising:** We may contact you to offer you additional services. You may opt out of receiving our promotional communications at any time by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link in them. This will not stop any service communications from us. 

###  With whom we share your information: 

  * **Your Survey questions and responses:** Generally we treat your questions and the responses to your surveys as your personal information and only share this information as detailed below or per your permission. 
  * **If Your Account Is Part of A Multiuser Subscription Plan:** Some of your account information, such as your surveys and activity will be visible to the master account admin and other sub-account members. 
  * **Service Providers:** We share your information with third parties who help us to provide you with our services including payment processors, hosting services, email service providers, communications providers, providers for our chat function and web traffic analytics tools. We grant these providers access to your information only to the extent necessary for them to perform their services to us. We also implement reasonable contractual and technical measure to ensure that your personal information is protected, used only for the provision of their services to us, and processed consistent with the terms of this privacy policy. 
  * **Advertising:** We may allow our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to use tracking technologies like cookies and web beacons to collect information about users who use the Services. The tracking technologies allow the third parties to deliver targeted advertisements of our products and services on other websites or on social media networks and gauge their effectiveness. 
  * **Merger, Transactions: Bankruptcy:** In the event that Umongous or its affiliates undergoes a corporate restructuring, enters into a merger, acquisition, sale or other transaction pursuant to which, Umongous or any portion of its assets or stock is acquired by or assigned to a third party, or if we are involved in a bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, liquidation, similar transaction or proceedings, your personal information, including the questions and answers of your survey may be among the items sold or otherwise transferred and may be shared with third parties, including buyers, service providers or law enforcement officials. 
  * **Law enforcement:** We will share your information with law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when (i) we are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or similar legal procedure, (ii) we need to do so to comply with law, (iii) if we believe in good faith that the disclosure of your personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity; (iv) to enforce this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use or to protect the security or integrity of our Services; and/or (v) to defend against legal claims or demands, exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Umongous, our users or others. 
  * **Per your express consent:** We may share your information for other reasons or purposes if you provide your permission for us to do so. 

###  Links to Other Web Sites 

Our Website includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Umongous. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit. 

###  Data Retention: 

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you Services. We will retain personal information about you for as long as necessary in order to provide the Services. We will retain and use this personal information only as long as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements and then delete it. 

Even if you delete your account, keep in mind that the deletion by our third-party providers may not be immediate and that the deleted information may persist in backup copies for up to 24 months or as required by legal requirements that apply to such third parties. Also, information that had already been shared with third parties may not be deleted by them. 

###  Data Security: 

Umongous has implemented commercially reasonable security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of your personal information under our control. For example, all personal information collected by us is transferred over https, we limit access to the information only to individuals who need the information to perform their duties and we use reliable third party providers to back up and personal information. However, regardless of the security measures we implement, transmission over the internet is not completely secure nor is any type of electronic storage and there is always a risk that your information may be accessed or used by unauthorized third parties. 

###  Your access and choices regarding your personal information: 

Correcting, Updating or Deleting Personal Information: 

You may access and update your registration information by logging into your account on the Website by clicking the account link in the menu bar, selecting the type of information that you wish to change, and typing in the corrected information. You may also exercise this right by contacting us at . If you wish to change your email address, contact us at  and we will be happy to assist you within 2 business days. We will respond to you within a reasonable time and, where appropriate, grant these rights to you. There rights are subject to some exceptions, including where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to your privacy, or where the rights of other individuals would be violated as a result. 

If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at . 

Correcting or Deleting Customer Testimonials: 

If you wish to update or delete a customer testimonial you had provided, you can contact us at . 

Choices regarding the collection of your information 

  * **Analytics:** You can control the information provided to Google and opt out of certain ads provided by Google by using of the of the methods set forth in http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners / or use the Google Analytics opt out browser add-on at http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en. 
  * **Cookies and other technologies:** Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser's directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. Turning off the browser's cookies will prevent web beacons from tracking your specific activity. The web beacon may still record an anonymous visit from your IP address, but unique information will not be recorded. If you do not want to receive tracking pixels, you will need to disable HTML images in your email client, and that may affect your ability to view images in other emails that you receive. To find out how to see what cookies have been set and how to reject and delete the cookies, please visit: http://www.aboutcookies.org. 
  * **Advertising:** You can understand which third parties have currently enabled cookies for your browser or mobile device and how to opt-out of some of those cookies by accessing http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp; http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or, if you're located in the European Union, at http://www.youronlinechoices.eu. from your browser and from your mobile device. Even if you opt out of targeted advertising you will continue to see advertising of a generic nature. 

###  Protection of Children's Privacy: 

The site is intended for adults. We do not intentionally or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 and we request that individuals under the age of 13 not submit any personal information on the site. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has created an account on the Website, we will promptly close that account and delete any submitted information. 

###  International Users: 

Umongous transfers, processes and stores information about you on servers located in Canada. By using our Website or the Services you understand and consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information to our facilities in Canada and to those third parties with whom we share it as described in this policy. You may revoke your consent at any time. Please note that if you revoke your consent to the transfer of the information to Canada, we may no longer be able to provide you our Services. 

###  Browser Do Not Track 

Our Website does not support Do Not Track at this time. Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference you can set in your web browser to indicate that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected across websites when you have not interacted with that service on the page. For all the details, including how to turn on Do Not Track, visit www.donottrack.us 

###  How We Notify You About Changes to Our Privacy Policy: 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, our Website, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our Website. 

###  How to Contact the Company Regarding Your Privacy Concerns: 

Company can be reached at any time by email at . It is our practice to respond to emails within 48 hours. If we do not respond within 48 hours, call us at 415-364-8601 and leave a message including your email address; we will respond to your voicemail within one business day. 

You can also write to us at: 

Umongous, Inc. 3000 Atrium Way, Suite 260, Mount Laurel, New Jersey, 08054. 

If you have any concerns or complaints regarding the processing of your personal data, please contact us as described below. You also have the option to resolve any dispute we have not adequately addressed through JAMS our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider, at no cost to you. You may contact them through https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim. 

Last updated: February 18, 2017
